first of it um with these boxes right
here the next boot camp is just going to
be even even easier I probably won't
even do a month ever again I'll probably
just do like two weeks um you know just
kind of explain it Box by box so you
know you guys are witnesses you guys are
just been but like the thing that I like
about the 30 days is like bro you bro we
literally like come on like we saw this
whole move together we called this whole
move together we saw this whole move
together we called this whole move
together we saw this pullback together
and we like you get what I mean like
it's just different 30 days you get me
it's a lot more work on me but whatever
I'm out for it um so like it's just kind
of like what what um you know what what
I look forward to so I mean definitely
it's it's this is my best one I think my
next one will be my best one um yeah you
know at this point it's just watch them
back every single video every single
week if you guys notice maybe you guys
are going to notice now this is all I
talk about every single week
this is this is week
one this is week
two and then this is week three with
week four that's literally it and even
in those weeks it was still you know
like it it takes some time because we
got to go from showing you guys examples
on a chart like this then actually going
on a Candlestick like it's like a it's a
whole mission but yeah this is this is
everything I've been teaching you for
the past four weeks
they can't believe yeah yeah I know
nobody's I can guarantee you nobody's
teaching this for for a fact nobody has
this on YouTube uh maybe there's
somebody out there teaching like this
but I don't know feel like the way that
I'm doing it nobody else is doing it
um so yeah again take a screenshot if
you guys haven't already um this I'm
going to put like a little star on the
telegram as the last recording and I'm
going to I'm going to make everything
look nice now CU all I have is the
telegram for the recordings but I'm
going to make a site where specifically
from you guys I think I might be
switching over from Discord to like a
different server like something
completely different it's like a lot
more like
professional um and then yeah you guys
again I highly recommend you guys still
get on your Zoom calls weekly um I try
to jump in once a week I'll drop a zoom
and then like you know try to like just
I'll do like a Sunday swings randomly
with you guys um kind of like pave the
road like oh guys this week this is my
top four you guys got it from here like
I'm I'm giving you guys kind of like
where the fish where like the fishing
spots are and then you know you figure
out how to Anchor there you figure out
how to put on your own bait how to do
all that stuff but I'm kind of telling
you where the fish have a high
probability of being BR I'm crazy with
these analogies I don't have to be a
poet or whatever analogy people
do all
right yes yes Joseph
yes F let me just thought there Wasing
get too